There are things that say to the world,
"I have a boyfriend and he's not made up."
Matching costumes, hickies, and sex tapes.
(Amy:)Pick one.
(Sheldon:)What's a hickey?
- How do I look?
- Fine.
(Bernadette:)Uh-oh. Is someone a little blue?
(Bernadette:)Come on, Howie, that's, like,
the funniest thing I've ever said in my life.
What do you say, you ready to go?
(Howard:)To tell you the truth,
I'm not really in the mood.
(Bernadette:)What are you talking about? It'll be fun,
your friends will be there.
(Howard:)Some friends. They all think I'm boring.
(Howard:)Maybe you should go without me.
(Bernadette:)No, if I'm there alone people might think
I'm just a really short person from Avatar.